as a solopreneur you wear multiple hats
one minute you're handling client email
the next you're busy in admin work or
chasing deadlines finding work life
balance can be tough while no tool can
solve them all the right tool can help
you stay organized and stay focused on
what matters here's why Flint boards is
a musthave tool for solopreneurs and how
it can balance workload maintain focus
and stay on time with all projects
first of all let's tackle Focus shifting
and workload mismanagement managing your
projects become much easier when you
know what needs to be done what to focus
on First and how much time you've got
Define your objectives at the very
beginning a detailed plan and clear
Milestones make sure you're always on
track with your
projects to ensure your project runs
smoothly break your entire project into
multiple stages
and then divide your project work into
manageable
[Music]
tasks with an achievable
deadline the priority level can
highlight what to focus on First and
what
not dividing big tasks into smaller
subtasks help you tackle them
effortlessly one step at a time besides
set an estimated time you need for each
task log the actual time spent on it and
challenge yourself to get faster with
each new task make your every task an
opportunity to improve that's how
managing your workload becomes a breeze
with fluent boards next up enhance
communication and boost collaboration
even if you work solo you still need to
connect with clients vendors and
contractors for many reasons using flu
board you can onboard them onto your
project board to share information
discussions and realtime collaboration
making it a central location for all
your conversations and ensuring you
never feel alone you can also attach any
necessary files to your
tasks keeping everything in order
features like the front-end portal make
project management easier even from the
front end of your WordPress site prefer
not to onboard others integrate with
tools like fluen CRM and pull your
client info directly onto your board
access them whenever you want or use
automation to notify them about each
progress don't want to do that either
it's integration with fluent forms can
save you create a
form map form
fields and share it with others now
every time they submit this form a task
will be created in into the defined
board and Stage having collaboration
sorted let's move on to reporting and
insights as a solar preneur tracking
performance like a pro is vital and
that's exactly what reports provide you
with the right tool you can always have
a complete overview of what's going on
what you have done and how things are
going as you can see flen boards checks
all the boxes improved workload
management elimination of focus shifting
realtime communication and collaboration
and significant Time Savings I must say
fluent boards is the go-to solution for
you and any solopreneur so to be one of
77% of high performing projects that use
a project management tool for successful
project completion grab FL boards now
[Music]